http://www.iri.com/company/legal/privacy

Solutions
BI & AnalyticsEmbedded BIBIRT IntegrationKNIME IntegrationSplunk IntegrationsCloud DashboardBI Tool AccelerationBig DataBig Data PackagingBig Data ProtectionBig Data ProvisioningStructured DataSemi & Unstructured DataWith/out HadoopUse CasesIoTBootcampBDaaSData GovernanceData MaskingData QualityTest DataForensicsRBACsStewardshipCOBITEnterprise Metadata ManagementMaster Data ManagementData IntegrationBuild New ETLSpeed Your ETLRe-Platform Your ETLSupercharge Your ETLFast & Easy IRI ETL ToolsETL & BeyondData MaskingAuditingCCPADLPFERPAGDPRHIPAAPCI DSSData Masking as a ServiceStatic Data MaskingDynamic Data MaskingTest DataData MigrationData Type ConversionFile Format ConversionDatabase MigrationData ReplicationData TransformationAggregateCross-CalculateCustom TransformsFormats/KeysLookupsMatch/JoinPivot/UnpivotRe-Map/ReformatScrub/CleanseSelect/FilterSort/MergeSubstringsType-ConvertDB OperationsCassandraDB2 UDBMongoDBMySQLOraclePostgreSQLSAP HANASnowflakeSQL ServerSybaseTeradataMetadata & MDMMetadataMetadata ManagementMaster DataMDMQuality & SecurityServicesSort Replacementsbin/sortJCL SORTMicro Focus COBOLNaturalSASUniKixTest DataBenchmarkingComplianceDB Test DataDB SubsettingDevOpsTest Files/ReportsTest Data VirtualizationTDaaSProducts
IRI Data Manager (Suite)IRI Data Protector (Suite)IRI Voracity (Platform)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesIRI CoSort (Transformation)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesSortCL ProgramSortCL MetadataCOBOL ToolsSort PluginsAPIsIRI FACT (Extraction)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesIRI NextForm (Migration)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesIRI RowGen (Test Data)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesIRI FieldShield (Masking)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesIRI CellShield (Excel)CellShield Personal Edition (PE) Add-InCellShield (EE)IRI DarkShield (Dark Data)OverviewFeatures & BenefitsTechnical DetailsWhy It's BetterPlatforms & PricingResourcesIRI Workbench (GUI)OverviewData SourcesDiscover DataDesign & Run JobsEdit & Share ProjectsEclipse FacilitiesVoracity GUICoSort GUIFACT GUIFieldShield GUINextForm GUIRowGen GUIFree Trial, Demo, QuoteFeature MatrixFree TrialLive DemoQuote RequestContactCustomers
IndustriesOverviewBFSICDI/eCommerceEnergyGovernmentHealthcareRetail/CPGTelco & CableTransportCase StudiesTestimonialsUser RolesBI Analyst & Data ScientistDBAOverviewCIO/IT ManagerETL/Solution ArchitectCompliance OfficerProgrammer & ISVLegacy ToolsUser GroupsSurveysData Masking QualifiersIT NeedsUser ReviewWebinarsPayment PortalServices
Professional ServicesProduct TrainingIRI HQ TrainingOn-Site TrainingSelf-Directed LearningCertificationCertificationVoracity CertificationCoSort CertificationFACT CertificationNextForm CertificationFieldShield CertificationCellShield EE CertificationDarkShield CertificationRowGen CertificationTechnical SupportCompany
About IRIDifferentiationHistoryLocationManagementMissionOutreachRecognitionCOVID-19 Policy & PrepHistory1970s1980s1990s2000s2010s2020sCareersAccount ManagerChannel ManagerMarketing ManagerSoftware DeveloperSupport EngineerInternshipsContact UsLegal NoticesCopyrightTrademarksDisclaimerCode of ConductPrivacy PolicyFAQsNews
Big Data BootcampPress ReleasesNewslettersSupport
Self-LearningSupport RequestLicense TransfersPartners
Expert ConsultantsBig DataCloudDW/BIData MaskingLegacy MigrationTest DataIndustry AlliancesInternational ResellersEmbed Opportunities
Solutions
BI & AnalyticsEmbedded BIBIRT IntegrationKNIME IntegrationSplunk IntegrationsCloud DashboardBI Tool AccelerationBig DataBig Data PackagingBig Data ProtectionBig Data ProvisioningStructured DataSemi & Unstructured DataWith/out HadoopUse CasesIoTBootcampBDaaSData GovernanceData MaskingData QualityTest DataForensicsRBACsStewardshipCOBITEnterprise Metadata ManagementMaster Data ManagementData IntegrationBuild New ETLSpeed Your ETLRe-Platform Your ETLSupercharge Your ETLFast & Easy IRI ETL ToolsETL & BeyondData MaskingAuditingCCPADLPFERPAGDPRHIPAAPCI DSSData Masking as a ServiceStatic Data MaskingDynamic Data MaskingTest DataData MigrationData Type ConversionFile Format ConversionDatabase MigrationData ReplicationData TransformationAggregateCross-CalculateCustom TransformsFormats/KeysLookupsMatch/JoinPivot/UnpivotRe-Map/ReformatScrub/CleanseSelect/FilterSort/MergeSubstringsType-ConvertDB OperationsCassandraDB2 UDBMongoDBMySQLOraclePostgreSQLSAP HANASnowflakeSQL ServerSybaseTeradataMetadata & MDMMetadataMetadata ManagementMaster DataMDMQuality & SecurityServicesSort Replacementsbin/sortJCL SORTMicro Focus COBOLNaturalSASUniKixTest DataBenchmarkingComplianceDB Test DataDB SubsettingDevOpsTest Files/ReportsTest Data VirtualizationTDaaSProducts
IRI Data Manager (Suite)IRI Data Protector (Suite)IRI Voracity (Platform)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesIRI CoSort (Transformation)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesSortCL ProgramSortCL MetadataCOBOL ToolsSort PluginsAPIsIRI FACT (Extraction)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesIRI NextForm (Migration)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesIRI RowGen (Test Data)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesIRI FieldShield (Masking)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesIRI CellShield (Excel)CellShield Personal Edition (PE) Add-InCellShield (EE)IRI DarkShield (Dark Data)OverviewFeatures & BenefitsTechnical DetailsWhy It's BetterPlatforms & PricingResourcesIRI Workbench (GUI)OverviewData SourcesDiscover DataDesign & Run JobsEdit & Share ProjectsEclipse FacilitiesVoracity GUICoSort GUIFACT GUIFieldShield GUINextForm GUIRowGen GUIFree Trial, Demo, QuoteFeature MatrixFree TrialLive DemoQuote RequestContactCustomers
IndustriesOverviewBFSICDI/eCommerceEnergyGovernmentHealthcareRetail/CPGTelco & CableTransportCase StudiesTestimonialsUser RolesBI Analyst & Data ScientistDBAOverviewCIO/IT ManagerETL/Solution ArchitectCompliance OfficerProgrammer & ISVLegacy ToolsUser GroupsSurveysData Masking QualifiersIT NeedsUser ReviewWebinarsPayment PortalServices
Professional ServicesProduct TrainingIRI HQ TrainingOn-Site TrainingSelf-Directed LearningCertificationCertificationVoracity CertificationCoSort CertificationFACT CertificationNextForm CertificationFieldShield CertificationCellShield EE CertificationDarkShield CertificationRowGen CertificationTechnical SupportCompany
About IRIDifferentiationHistoryLocationManagementMissionOutreachRecognitionCOVID-19 Policy & PrepHistory1970s1980s1990s2000s2010s2020sCareersAccount ManagerChannel ManagerMarketing ManagerSoftware DeveloperSupport EngineerInternshipsContact UsLegal NoticesCopyrightTrademarksDisclaimerCode of ConductPrivacy PolicyFAQsNews
Big Data BootcampPress ReleasesNewslettersSupport
Self-LearningSupport RequestLicense TransfersPartners
Expert ConsultantsBig DataCloudDW/BIData MaskingLegacy MigrationTest DataIndustry AlliancesInternational ResellersEmbed Opportunities
SolutionsBI & AnalyticsEmbedded BIBIRT IntegrationKNIME IntegrationSplunk IntegrationsCloud DashboardBI Tool AccelerationBig DataBig Data PackagingBig Data ProtectionBig Data ProvisioningStructured DataSemi & Unstructured DataWith/out HadoopUse CasesIoTBootcampBDaaSData GovernanceData MaskingData QualityTest DataForensicsRBACsStewardshipCOBITEnterprise Metadata ManagementMaster Data ManagementData IntegrationBuild New ETLSpeed Your ETLRe-Platform Your ETLSupercharge Your ETLFast & Easy IRI ETL ToolsETL & BeyondData MaskingAuditingCCPADLPFERPAGDPRHIPAAPCI DSSData Masking as a ServiceStatic Data MaskingDynamic Data MaskingTest DataData MigrationData Type ConversionFile Format ConversionDatabase MigrationData ReplicationData TransformationAggregateCross-CalculateCustom TransformsFormats/KeysLookupsMatch/JoinPivot/UnpivotRe-Map/ReformatScrub/CleanseSelect/FilterSort/MergeSubstringsType-ConvertDB OperationsCassandraDB2 UDBMongoDBMySQLOraclePostgreSQLSAP HANASnowflakeSQL ServerSybaseTeradataMetadata & MDMMetadataMetadata ManagementMaster DataMDMQuality & SecurityServicesSort Replacementsbin/sortJCL SORTMicro Focus COBOLNaturalSASUniKixTest DataBenchmarkingComplianceDB Test DataDB SubsettingDevOpsTest Files/ReportsTest Data VirtualizationTDaaSProductsIRI Data Manager (Suite)IRI Data Protector (Suite)IRI Voracity (Platform)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesIRI CoSort (Transformation)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesSortCL ProgramSortCL MetadataCOBOL ToolsSort PluginsAPIsIRI FACT (Extraction)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesIRI NextForm (Migration)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesIRI RowGen (Test Data)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesIRI FieldShield (Masking)OverviewFeaturesTechnical DetailsGUIPlatforms & PricingWhy It's BetterResourcesIRI CellShield (Excel)CellShield Personal Edition (PE) Add-InCellShield (EE)IRI DarkShield (Dark Data)OverviewFeatures & BenefitsTechnical DetailsWhy It's BetterPlatforms & PricingResourcesIRI Workbench (GUI)OverviewData SourcesDiscover DataDesign & Run JobsEdit & Share ProjectsEclipse FacilitiesVoracity GUICoSort GUIFACT GUIFieldShield GUINextForm GUIRowGen GUIFree Trial, Demo, QuoteFeature MatrixFree TrialLive DemoQuote RequestContactCustomersIndustriesOverviewBFSICDI/eCommerceEnergyGovernmentHealthcareRetail/CPGTelco & CableTransportCase StudiesTestimonialsUser RolesBI Analyst & Data ScientistDBAOverviewCIO/IT ManagerETL/Solution ArchitectCompliance OfficerProgrammer & ISVLegacy ToolsUser GroupsSurveysData Masking QualifiersIT NeedsUser ReviewWebinarsPayment PortalServicesProfessional ServicesProduct TrainingIRI HQ TrainingOn-Site TrainingSelf-Directed LearningCertificationCertificationVoracity CertificationCoSort CertificationFACT CertificationNextForm CertificationFieldShield CertificationCellShield EE CertificationDarkShield CertificationRowGen CertificationTechnical SupportCompanyAbout IRIDifferentiationHistoryLocationManagementMissionOutreachRecognitionCOVID-19 Policy & PrepHistory1970s1980s1990s2000s2010s2020sCareersAccount ManagerChannel ManagerMarketing ManagerSoftware DeveloperSupport EngineerInternshipsContact UsLegal NoticesCopyrightTrademarksDisclaimerCode of ConductPrivacy PolicyFAQsNewsBig Data BootcampPress ReleasesNewslettersSupportSelf-LearningSupport RequestLicense TransfersPartnersExpert ConsultantsBig DataCloudDW/BIData MaskingLegacy MigrationTest DataIndustry AlliancesInternational ResellersEmbed Opportunities
IRI Privacy Policy
Data Collection, Retention, and Use
Next Steps
Home
»
Company
»
Legal Notices
»
Privacy Policy
Quick Links +
+
About IRI
Differentiation
History
+
Location
Privacy Policy
The IRI.COM website, blog.iri.com (iri.com/blog) and team.iri.com sites (hereinafter referred to as the "Service") are owned and operated by Innovative Routines International, Inc. a private, independently owned and operated software vendor (ISV) originally founded in 1978. IRI uses this page to inform website visitors of our industry-standard policies related to the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information of anyone deciding to use the site or request information on our products and services from us.
If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy.
Information Collection and Use
The Personal Information that we collect may be used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
For a better experience while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your name, phone number, email and/or postal address. The information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you.
Log Data. Whenever you visit our Service, the website automatically collects information that your browser sends to the web server. That is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser version, pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.
Cookies. Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer's hard drive. Our website may use these “cookies” to collection information and to improve our Service. If it uses a cookie, you will have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Service Providers. We may employ third-party companies and individuals to: facilitate our Service, provide the Service on our behalf; perform Service-related services; or, assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. These third parties may have access to the aforementioned Personal Information which may be needed only to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.
Security
We value your trust in providing us any Personal Information you decide to share, and thus strive to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. Remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Links to Other Sites. Our Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.
Children's Privacy. Our Services do not address anyone under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 18. In the case we discover that a child under 18 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to perform the necessary actions.
Compliance with Data Privacy Laws. IRI complies with the data portability and right to be forgotten provisions of the GDPR and similar data privacy laws pertaining to on-demand data de-identification and deletion. Please contact us if you have a specific request to have your information searched and scrubbed from our systems, unsubscribe from a newsletter, etc.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting new Privacy Policy provisions in whole or in part on this page. These changes are effective once posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
Request More Information
Live Chat
* indicates a required field.
IRI does NOT share your information.
Solutions
BI & AnalyticsBig DataData GovernanceData IntegrationData MaskingData MigrationData TransformationDB OperationsMetadata & MDMSort ReplacementsTest Data
Products
IRI Data Manager (Suite)IRI Data Protector (Suite)IRI Voracity (Platform)IRI CoSort (Transformation)IRI FACT (Extraction)IRI NextForm (Migration)IRI RowGen (Test Data)IRI FieldShield (Masking)IRI CellShield (Excel)IRI DarkShield (Dark Data)IRI Workbench (GUI)Free Trial, Demo, Quote
Customers
IndustriesCase StudiesTestimonialsUser RolesLegacy ToolsUser GroupsSurveysWebinarsPayment Portal
Services
Professional ServicesProduct TrainingCertificationTechnical Support
Company
About IRICOVID-19 Policy & PrepHistoryCareersContact UsLegal NoticesFAQs
Expert ConsultantsIndustry AlliancesInternational ResellersEmbed Opportunities
Copyright © 2020 Innovative Routines International (IRI), Inc.
